斯图尔特
Oh, hey, Stuart,
我有个太空之旅的纪念品要送你
I got you a little souvenir from my trip to space.
霍华德  你真好
Well, Howard, that's very nice of you.
难说哦  先打开看看吧
Yeah, maybe. Open it first.
我的宇航局官方肖像画哦
It's my official NASA portrait.
"致斯图尔特  你的漫画店是店上之店
"To Stuart, your comic book store is out of this world.
就像画里的人是人上之人 一样"
Just like the guy in this picture was."
他还觉得沃尔格林[连锁药店]
For the record, he also thinks the Walgreens
以及干洗店也是店上之店呢
and the dry cleaners are out of this world.
此言差矣
That's not true.
在沃尔格林时
At the Walgreens,
我称赞他们的药  "甩众店于九霄云外"
I was "over the moon" for their store-brand antacids.
斯图尔特  你开始为万圣节派对做准备啦
Stuart, I see you're getting ready for your Halloween party.
这可是我每年的泡妞时节呢
Yeah, it's my annual attempt to meet women.
希望第九次可以手到妞来
Ninth time's the charm.
需要我帮忙吗
Would you like me to help?
置办派对  我可是有不少锦囊妙计哦
I do have a certain je ne sais quois when it comes to soirees.
谢了  "锦囊妙计"我付不起
Thanks, but I can't afford je ne sais quois.
单纯"妙计"要多少钱
How much for just quois?
不用担心钱
You know, you don't worry about money.
-钱的事交给我  -真的吗
- I'll take care of everything. - Really?
对啊  库萨"派"里  顾名思义就是办派对之王啊
Yeah, you'll love it. Ain't no party like a Koothra-party.
你们知道什么绝不算派对吗
But you know what wasn't a party?
火箭发射前的一晚
That hotel in Kazakhstan
我被安排入住哈萨克斯坦的酒店
they put you up in before the launch.
那可是我待在地球的最后一晚
I mean, it's your last night on Earth.
还以为会送个黄片频道看看呢
You'd think you'd get one porn channel.
你发现霍华德可以把任何话题
Have you noticed that Howard can take any topic
都拿来炫耀去过太空吗
and use it to remind you that he went to space?
这假设有意思
Interesting hypothesis.
套用科学的方法
Let's apply the scientific method,
-做实验证明吧  -没问题
-perform an experiment. -Okay.
霍华德  今晚想去哪里吃饭呀
Hey, Howard, any thoughts on where we should get dinner?
哪里都行  别去太空站就好
Anywhere but the Space Station.
运气好时  也就一包肉饼
On a good day, dinner was a bag full of meat loaf.
不过去那里  不为美食
But, hey, you don't go there for the food,
只为美景嘛
you go there for the view.
太厉害了
It's fascinating.
让我再试试  看结果是否相同
Let me see if I can duplicate the result.
霍华德  我一直觉得
Howard, I've always thought
人们太看轻柠檬了
the lemon was an underrated fruit.
有何高见
Care to weigh in?
其实还真没有
Not really.
遗憾啊
Oh, well.
有人笑过联合号太空舱像颗柠檬
You know, people say the Soyuz capsule was a lemon.
但好歹它带我上过天  又平安返航
But, hey, that baby got me to space and back.
能在起司工厂度过闺蜜之夜
Ladies night at the Cheesecake Factory.
还有比这更美好的时刻吗
Does it get any better than this?
希望会有
I hope so.
提问
Question.
你觉得你丈夫对高领衣服的热爱
Do you think your husband's fondness for turtlenecks
是在缅怀被犹太割礼掉的包皮吗
is an expression of longing for his missing foreskin?
看样子是没有
It's not getting any better.
是莱纳德
Uch. It's Leonard.
想拉我去买万圣节化装服
He wants to go costume shopping later.
-你不是喜欢过万圣节的吗  -是啊
- I thought you liked Halloween. - I do, it's just
但他想去那个漫画店的派对
he wants to go to that party at the comic book store.
在那里混的很多男的都怪怪的
A lot of the guys that hang out there are kind of creepy.
-比如我老公嘛吗  -以及我男朋友吗
- Like my husband? - And my boyfriend?
艾米  抱歉
I'm, I'm sorry, Amy.
你刚说到霍华德的包皮什么来着
You were saying something about Howard's foreskin?
少来了  你必须参加那个派对
Nice try, but you have to go to that party
-因为我们俩都会去  -我会去啊
- 'cause we're going. - Yeah, I'm gonna go.
只是那里并非我心中的欢乐派对
It's just not my idea of a good time.
莱纳德也常牺牲自己  哄你开心啊
Leonard does thing he doesn't like to make you happy.
他是我男朋友  这是他的义务
Yeah, he's my boyfriend. Isn't that, like, his job?
那你的义务是什么
Then what's your job?
给他哄我开心的机会啊
Letting him make me happy.
我觉得感情上
I just think in relationships
你付出多少才能得到多少
you get back what you put into them.
也不是永远都这样
That's not always true.
昨晚我对谢尔顿施展了我的迷魂眼
Last night I gave Sheldon my best come-hither look,
结果他对我解释了
and he responded by explaining how
人类种植稻米的起源
wheat came to be cultivated.
我是可以努力试试啦
I guess I could probably try a little harder.
你可以从对他的工作表现出兴趣开始
You could start by taking an interest in his work.
-那有点难度啊  -为什么
- Yeah, that's kind of a problem. - Why?
我搞不懂他做什么工作啊
Not really clear on what he does.
他是个实验物理学家
He's an experimental physicist.
这我也不太理解是什么
Yeah, I'm not really clear on what that means.
他提出假设  然后设计实验
He takes hypotheses and designs protocols
从而验证其正确性
to determine their accuracy.
很好  现在我更搞不懂了
Yeah, you're really just making it worse.
你想喝什么茶
What kind of tea would you like?
我想喝  绿茶混柠檬活力茶
I think I'm gonna try green tea mixed with lemon zinger.
两茶一杯吗
Two tea bags in one cup?
又不是在狂欢派对
You're not at a rave.
谢尔顿  我在想件事
So, listen, Sheldon, I was thinking,
这次是我们确定关系后
since this is gonna be our first
首次共度的万圣节派对
Halloween party as boyfriend and girlfriend,
我想我们准备一套情侣化装服会不错吧
I thought it might be fun for us to go in a couples costume.
完全同意
I couldn't agree more.
真的吗  这不像是
Really? I find that inconsistent
我认识的你会说的话啊
with everything I know about you.
这次恰恰相反
Oh, oh, on the contrary.
情侣化装服可是当情侣少有的
Couples costumes are one of the few benefits
好处之一呢
of being in a relationship.
想象一下
Now imagine this:
你我一同步入斯图尔特的派对
you and I entering Stuart's party
众人目光聚焦在全美最有爱
and all eyes turn to see America's most beloved
-最迷人的情侣身上  -是吗
- and glamorous couple. - Yeah?
R2-D2与C-3PO
R2-D2 and C-3PO!
我要扮3PO
Dibs on 3PO.
谢尔顿  我说情侣化装服
Sheldon, when I said couples costume,
是指像罗密欧与朱丽叶
I meant like Romeo and Juliet
或是灰姑娘和白马王子
or Cinderella and Prince Charming,
而不是两个机器人
not two robots
而且我根本不喜欢那部白痴电影
from some silly movie I don't even like.
小心说话啊  同志
Okay!
这次我放过你
I'm gonna let that slide
就当你是要喝双茶包而昏了头
because I know you're hopped up on tea bags.
我总是为你牺牲自我
I make compromises for you all the time.
但就这一次
Just this once,
我们不能找个两个人都满意的方案吗
can't we find something that we're both happy with?
好吧  那打扮成20世纪
Fine. How about one of the most beguiling
最有吸引力和影响力的一对如何
and influential couples of the 20th century?
比尔·休利特和戴维·帕卡德是惠普(HP)公司创始人
两者均为男性
休利特和帕卡德
Hewlett and Packard.
我要扮休利特
Dibs on Hewlett.
干嘛  你想扮休利特吗
What, you want to be Hewlett?
有人在吗
Anybody home?
稀客稀客啊  你来干嘛
Hey-hey-hey, what are you doing here?
我只顺路过来跟你打声招呼
I just thought I'd stop by and say hello.
真是个美好惊喜呀
Oh, what a nice surprise.
你从来没见过我的实验室吧
I don't think you've ever seen my lab before.
对啊  早就该来了
No, I know. It's long overdue.
那你在干嘛呢
So, what ya doing?
最好不是在造机器人女友
Better not be building a robot girlfriend.
当然不是
No.
不过霍华德在遇见伯纳黛特前
Although Howard was making some real strides
的确在那领域取得了不少进步
in that area until he met Bernadette.
-什么  你在开玩笑吧  -没有
- What? You're kidding. - Nope.
电子丽莎3000现在正乖乖待着箱子里
Now the Lisatronic 3000 just sits in a box
等着主人来电呢
waiting for the phone to ring.
哇  这里面是什么呀
Ooh! What's going on in here?
别别别  千万别打开看
Oh, no, no, no, don't look in there.
干嘛  是秘密吗
What, is it secret?
不  是氮激光器
No, it's a nitrogen laser.
看一眼  你的眼珠就会变成半熟的鸡蛋
It'll cook your eyeball like a soft-boiled egg.
或许你该在箱子上标记一下
Oh. You might want to put a sign on it.
标记在这里
Sign right there.
"危险"  没错  没错
Ah. "Danger," sure, sure.
那个又是什么
Yeah. What's, what's that?
那是集成离子阱
Uh, that is an integrated ion trap
和飞行时间质谱仪
and time-of-flight mass spectrometer.
哇  高科技含量
Wow. High-techie-techie.
那这个小玩意是什么
What's this little box?
那是削铅笔机
That is a pencil sharpener.
哦  低科技含量
Ooh, low-techie-techie.
那你现在在研究什么呢
So, what are you working on right now?
-其实还蛮了不起的哦  -是吗
- It's actually pretty neat. - Yeah?
是啊  这是正投影全息显示
Yeah. It's a front-projected holographic display
加上手指激光跟踪器
combined with laser-based finger tracking.
来  我给你演示
Here, I'll show you.
我们把铅笔放在这里
We'll just put this pencil over here.
削得很尖  刚才的小玩意挺管用
Sharp. Thanks to the machine we saw earlier.
非常好
Very good.
然后激光会映射出反射面
And then a laser will map the reflective surface...
瞧瞧
and voil?
哇  真是太不可思议了
Wow. That is amazing.
弦理论中  有个基本概念
You know, there's a foundational idea in string theory
宇宙可能是一张全息图
that the whole universe may be a hologram.
这话什么意思
What do you mean?
全息原理提出的观点是
Well, the holographic principle suggests that
人类每天在三维空间感受的一切
what we all experience every day in three dimensions
可能只是宇宙最遥远的地方的
may really just be information
全息投影
on a surface located
我们感受到的宇宙其实是外界的信息
at the farthest reaches of our cosmos.
所以有可能我们的生活
So it's possible that our lives are
真的只是在宇宙这张
really just acting out a painting
最大的画布上表演绘画而已
on the largest canvas in the universe.
怎么了
What?
有时我会忘了你有多聪明
Sometimes I forget how smart you are.
你真应该经常来
You should visit more often.
你要干嘛
What are you doing?
把衣服脱掉
Take off your clothes.
现在啊  在这里吗
What? Here? Now?
-对  你有意见吗  -没有没有
- Yeah. You got a problem with that? - No, no.
真是疯狂啊
It's kind of crazy.
我从来没再实验室搞过
I've never fooled around in the lab before.
-真的没有吗  -有
- Really? Never? - No.
我跟电子丽莎试过
I did have a shot with the Lisatronic,
但是她的电源延长线不够长
but the extension cord wasn't long enough.
趁我还没忘  我想听听你们
Before I forget, I'd like your opinion on the menus
对万圣节菜单的意见
I've prepared for the Halloween party.
主题是"怪兽食物"
The theme is "Food that goes bump in the night."
"黑森林火腿湖怪兽"
"Creature from the Black Forest Ham Lagoon."
酷斯拉芝麻面包
On Sesame seed Bunzillas.
"死蓉面包之夜"
"Night of the Living Garlic Bread"?
笑点在"面包"音似"死亡"[英语]
It's funny because "bread" sounds like "dead."
抱歉  但这些都是普通的食物
I'm sorry, but these are just ordinary foods
不过是名字换成无聊的双关语
with the names bent into tortured puns.
菜色本身完全没有万圣节的感觉
The dishes themselves are in no way Halloweenie.
万圣节的感觉[万圣香肠]
Ooh, Hallow-weenies!
这双关取得不错
That's a good one.
这个跟我的"吸血鬼通心粉"很搭
They'll pair nicely with my "Draculoni and Cheese."
我真是天才啊
How do I do it?!
我突然想起  我打算
That reminds me, I was thinking about
穿我的太空衣去
wearing my NASA jumpsuit as a costume.
但我觉得大家可能会说
But then I realized everyone would be, like,
"你的化装服呢
"Where's your costume?
为什么你穿工作服来啊  傻子"
Why are you wearing your work clothes, you nut?"
伙计们  好呀
Hello, boys.
你在笑什么
What are you smiling at?
没什么
Nothing.
你们知道哪里什么都没有吗
You know where's there's a lot of nothing.
太空嘛
Space.
天啊  睡在床上不浮起来的感觉真好
Boy, it's nice to sleep in a bed with gravity again.
我有告诉过你  某晚我的牙保持器
Did I tell you about the night my retainer floated out
飘出我的嘴巴  飘进密封舱里吗
of my mouth and into the air lock?
有  你提过一两次吧
Yeah, you mentioned it once or twice.
我们终于团聚
So, here we are,
好一对新婚小夫妻
just a couple of young newlyweds.
做点什么好呢
What to do?
对  你  做  点  什  么  好
What to do to you?
宇航员沃罗威茨  上床报到
Astronaut Wolowitz, reporting for booty.
"推进器"准备
Preparing thrusters.
"火箭"成功升空
We have liftoff.
睡袍是否能"脱离"了
Are we clear to jettison that nightgown?
够了  我们得谈谈了
Okay, we need to talk.
谈什么
What?
华仔  我知道你登上了太空
Howie, I know you went to space.
我由衷地为你骄傲
I'm incredibly proud of you.
可你最好不要
But you might want to try
老把这件事挂在嘴边
and not bring it up every minute.
我没有总是提这事啊
I don't talk about it every minute.
今晚吃饭时你就聊了整整一个小时
Tonight at dinner you went on about it for an hour straight.
那不然聊什么
What was I supposed to talk about?
那餐馆叫约翰"火箭"啊
We were eating at Johnny Rockets.
我是说  大家都有点厌倦这话题了
I'm just saying, people are getting a little tired of it.
所以我完成了如此壮举
So, I did this amazing thing
还不准我念叨两句了吗
and I'm never allowed to mention it?
你当然可以提
Of course you can.
但更好的方式是
But maybe a good rule would be
等别人先提起这件事
to wait for people to bring it up.
好  没问题
Okay, no problem.
我不会再主动聊了
It won't happen again.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
你都不知道我做过多少次
I can't tell you how many times I dreamed
和你同床的梦  当我在...
I was in bed here with you when I was...
你懂的
you know.
怎么  连指一下也不行吗
What, I can't even point?
总的来说  这就是所谓的磁悬浮技术
So, basically, this is what's called maglev technology.
运用超强的电磁体
It uses very powerful electromagnets
制造出能对抗重力的磁悬浮力
to create a force strong enough to overcome gravity.
拿着这个
Here, you hold this.
-好重啊  -没错
- Whoa! That's heavy. - Yeah.
你没带什么珠宝首饰吧
Oh, uh, you don't have on any jewelry, do you?
没带  怎么了
No. Why?
上次有个研究生忘了摘"环"
A grad student forgot to take out one of his piercings.
如今他在排队等着
Now he's on a transplant list
移植和他匹配的乳头呢
waiting for a nipple his size.
看好了
Now watch this.
真是太酷了
That is very cool.
有时候我会开启仪器
Sometimes I like to turn this on
然后假装我是无敌坏蛋万磁王
and pretend I'm the super villain Magneto.
你这么说就不酷了  莱纳德
It's getting a little less cool, Leonard.
其实我只是一个特别聪明的科学家
But what I really am is a very smart scientist
身怀宇宙力学知识
who understands the mechanics of the universe
身穿你买的性感黑色小裤裤
and is wearing the sexy black underwear you bought him.
这就对了
There we go.
我觉得这次派对的拍照间
So, I thought the photo booth for the party
可以布置成恐怖的木乃伊之墓
could either be creepy like a mummy's tomb,
或者是《神秘博士》里的塔迪斯一样也不错
or they also have the Tardis from Doctor Who.
塔迪斯可不行
A Tardis makes no sense.
它是科幻小说里的时间机器
It's a time machine from a science-fiction show.
和万圣节扯不上关系
It has nothing to do with Halloween.
尽管如此  如果你不搞个塔迪斯来
That being said, if you don't get a Tardis,
你和你的派对就弱爆了
you stink and your party stinks.
你喜欢哪一种
Do you have a preference?
无所谓  就塔迪斯吧
I don't care. Get the Tardis.
太好了  这次派对一定超好玩
Yes! This party just became a major rager.
对了  我能借一下你的皮鞭和软呢帽吗
Oh, by the way, can I borrow your bullwhip and fedora?
行啊  随便你
Yeah, sure, whatever.
我想打扮成
I was thinking of dressing up as
印第安纳·琼斯的棕皮肤私生子
Indiana Jones' mocha-skinned love child.
印度·琼斯
"Indian" Jones.
很有哏
Clever.
你怎么了
What's wrong with you?
没怎么呀
Nothing.
霍华德  我还得策划派对呢
Oh, Howard, I've got a party to plan.
别让我费劲逼问你了
Don't make me pull it out of you.
好吧  说就说
Okay, here it is.
伯纳黛特说你们都特别烦我
Bernadette said you guys are all sick of me
老提上太空的事
talking about my trip to space.
这是真的吗
Is that true?
-不是  -是
- No. - Yes.
我俩的处理方式貌似相左啊
We seem to have different approaches here.
我是准备诚实地帮助他
I was going for helpful honesty.
你这是什么招数呢
I have no idea what you're doing.
我这叫当好人
It's called being nice.
好吧  如果你当好人
Okay. If you think being nice
就可以让他闭嘴  那我也当好人吧
will get him to shut up, I'll try it.
好了各位  没关系的
You know what, guys? Never mind.
我再也不提我这辈子最伟大的成就
I just won't talk about the greatest achievement
就是了
of my life ever again.
你瞧  不攻自破了
Look at that, the problem solved itself.
小崽子们好啊
Hello, boys.
我们装扮成
What if we were to go
餐桌最佳拍档"盐和胡椒"如何
as dinner table favorites salt and pepper?
你明知道我吃多了盐就水肿
You know salt makes me retain water
而我威廉表哥在胡椒工厂事故中被磨死了
and my cousin William was ground to death in a pepper factory accident.
我们扮"破烂小安和破烂安迪"吧
How about Raggedy Ann and Andy?
我小时候特别喜欢他们
I loved them growing up.
我不敢苟同
No, I don't think so.
那些破娃娃代表了我最不爱的三件事
Those dolls represent three things I do not care for:
小丑  小孩和破烂
clowns, children and raggediness.
-我觉得没戏了  -不行
- I think it's a lost cause. - No.
在这世上  有几件事能向大家证明
There are certain things that say to the world,
"我的男朋友是真实存在的"
"I have a boyfriend, and he's not made up."
情侣装
Matching costumes,
吻痕  以及性爱录影带
hickeys and sex tapes.
你选一个吧
Pick one.
什么是吻痕
What's a hickey?
我美不
How do I look?
还行
Fine.
哎呀  有人不开心吗[蓝色]
Uh-oh, is someone a little blue?
拜托  华仔  这可是我这辈子说过
Come on, Howie, that's like the funniest thing
最搞笑的话了
I've ever said in my life.
怎么样  可以走了吗
What do you say? You ready to go?
说实话  我没啥心情去
To tell you the truth, I'm not really in the mood.
说什么呢  会很好玩的
What are you talking about? It'll be fun.
你所有的朋友都会去
All your friends'll be there.
是  所谓的朋友  他们都觉得我很无趣
Yeah, some friends. They all think I'm boring.
也许你应该一个人去
Maybe you should go without me.
不  如果我一个人去  人家会以为
No, if I'm there alone, people might think
我是《阿凡达》里的小矮子
I'm just a really short person from Avatar.
抱歉  我就是不想去
I'm sorry. I just don't want to go.
我刚花了三小时把自己涂成蓝色
Hey, I just spent the last three hours coloring myself blue.
我"蓝密处"的蓝色得洗一个月才会掉呢
I'm gonna be washing paint out of my Smurf for a month!
好吧
Fine.
两周前我还是宇航员
Two weeks ago I was an astronaut.
好啦  你现在是蓝精灵  快走
Yeah, well, now you're a Smurf. Keep walking.
我的天  你们好可爱
Oh, my God, you guys look adorable!
谢谢  你们也是
Thanks, so do you.
你扮的是放荡女警吗
Slutty cop?
不  性感女警
No, sexy cop.
放荡女警的行头只有超短裙和两个徽章遮胸
Slutty cop only came with a skirt and two badges.
你扮的是爱因斯坦吗
And Albert Einstein?
对  稍后她会逮捕我
Ja, und later she's going to arrest me
因为我超速超过光年了
for goink fashter zen da shpeed of light.
我们在车里说过了  不准有口音
I thought we said in the car, no accents?
抱歉  警官
Sorry, Officer.
你好
Hello!
好棒的派对
It's a great party!
谢谢
Thank you!
怪兽食物  好有意思
The monster foods, they're really fun.
是的  谢谢
Oh, yes, thank you.
我喜欢想出有意思的事  因为我是有意思的人
I like to think of fun things like that because I'm fun.
我完全没有临床忧郁症
I'm not clinically depressed at all.
谢尔顿  进来
Sheldon, get in here!
我应该选吻痕的
I should've picked hickey.
瞧你们俩
Hey, hey, look at you guys!
我是破烂安娃娃  他是破烂C-3PO
I'm Raggedy Ann, and he's Raggedy C-3PO.
这是妥协  我输了
It was a compromise. I lost.
斯图尔特居然到处招摇  将派对
Can you believe Stuart's walking around
成功的功劳全揽在他一人身上
taking credit for this party?
谁在乎啊
Who cares?
你这么说是什么意思
What do you mean "Who cares"?
看看我的心血
Look at what I pulled off here.
DJ够劲爆
The deejay's on fire,
后面房间有个塔迪斯照相亭
there's a Tardis photo booth in the back room,
还有  食物棒的不得了
and, oh, my God, the food!
斯图尔特还想命名为"卡夫德古拉通心粉"
Stuart wanted Kraft Draculoni and cheese.
你说得对  派对棒极了
You're right, the party's fantastic.
求你  再多说说
Please, tell me more.
我这周还没听够呢
I haven't heard enough about it all week
听这个话题永远不会腻
because hearing about that never gets old!
这又是因为太空那件事吗
Is this about the space thing again?
我不允许谈这个话题
Well, I'm not allowed to talk about it,
但既然你提了  我上过太空
but since you brought it up, I went to space!
太空  太空  太空  我上过太空
Space, space, space! Space, space, space!
醉鬼蓝精灵
Whoa, Drinky Smurf.
过来我们说两句
Can I talk to you for a second?
好了  我有麻烦了
Great, now I'm in trouble.
你开心了吧
You happy?!
你  给我出去
You, out!
你太没礼貌了
You are being very rude!
我才不是  他们才没礼貌
No, I'm not. They're all being rude.
你也没礼貌
And you're being rude.
我  我做了什么
Me? What did I do?
"华仔
"Oh, Howie...
别再说这么多太空的事了
Stop talking about space so much.
没人喜欢听"
Nobody likes it."
我说话才不是那样
I don't sound like that.
你是我老婆
You're my wife.
你应该支持我才对
You're supposed to be on my side.
我一直是支持你的啊
I'm always on your side.
那你为什么不让我炫耀这事
Then why are you trying to take this away from me?
成为一名宇航员
Being an astronaut is
是我这辈子能做的最酷的事
the coolest thing I'm ever gonna do.
如果我不再说这个  那我只是...
If I stop talking about it, then I'm just...
只是什么
Just what?
只是以前无趣的霍华德·沃罗威茨了
Just plain old Howard Wolowitz again.
以前无趣的他  是我认识的最好的男人
Plain old Howard Wolowitz is the best guy I know.
你只是说了安慰我
You're just saying that.
我不是  我嫁给了他
No, I'm not. I married him.
特意的哦
On purpose.
过来啦
Come here.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
没什么热闹可瞧
Nothing to see here.
性感女警在执行公务
Just sexy police business.
我只是跟她解释相对论
Just explaining the theory of relativity.
"两次"哦
Twice.
在看什么呢
Hey, what you watching?
不知道
I don't know.
拉杰发了我一段巴兹·奥尔德林的视频[著名宇航员]
Raj sent me some video of Buzz Aldrin.
给你  这是银河牌巧克力棒
Here you go. It's a Milky Way.
银河系是太空里的星系
The Milky Way's a galaxy in space.
我上过太空哦
I've been in space.
这是火星牌巧克力棒
Here's a Mars bar.
我是个宇航员
I'm an astronaut.
这是月亮甜饼
And this one's a Moon Pie.
我曾在月亮上漫步
I walked on the Moon.
你做过什么
What have you done?
好啦  我懂了
Okay, I get it.